

Thejas Malenahalli Niranjan

Software Developer

Software engineer with self-motivated hands on experience in full stack Development and also a Ethical hacker who wants to be associated with an organisation that provides career development opportunities as a Developer and an environment to enable me to contribute to its growth.

Skills:



HTML



PYTHON



CSS



CYBER SECURITY



JAVASCRIPT



DJANGO



BOOTSTRAPt



SEO

AWS GIT



POSTGRESQL

Contact



(: +4917684349868

: emailme@thejasmn.com

() : Schneller Strasse 112a, Berlin 12439, Germany.



(#) : www.thejasmn.com





Work Experience

Logistics Employee

sept 2022- Present(Part-time) - Amazon Sortation Center, Berlin, Germany.

- Quality inspection and scanning package for required destination.
- loading and unloading goods checking for CPT packets.

Founder

April 2021 - Oct 2022- WAS Techno Developers, India

- Innovation, Research, Creative, Cost Effective, Time management.
- Experience in Situations handling and good at teamwork.
- Developing websites, applications and hosting in server and teaching python and cyber security for students in my startup.
- Created Local-mart application and failed in marketing due to financial crisis.
- Good at Pyhton full stack and Cyber Security

Associate developer

Jan - mar 2021 - Globalentitycore, India

- Directs software design and development
- Web-scrapping projects using python with beautiful soup.
- Team work

Education

Masters in Computer Science

IU International University of applied science Dec 2021 - Present Berlin, Germany

B.E: Electronics and Communications Engineering

BGS Institute of Technology Aug 2017 - Jul 2021. CGPA - 6.20 Bellur Cross, Karnataka, India

12th Class

Alvas Comp Pu College Jul 2015 - Mar 2017, 82.83% Moodbidri, Karnataka, India

10th Class

Sri Ramakrishna English Medium High School Jul 2014 - Apr 2015, 76.48% Hosanagara, Karnataka, India

Languages

Kannada: Native

English : Advance read and write

German: Beginner A1